Subscribe to the YouTube channel All Bank
Counter.com and press the bell button
to watch the video first Friends,
in this video we will tell you
important information related to your IDFC Bank account
Hello friends, today we will tell you
how you can change your group health insurance policy online from home using ICICI Bank's iMobile application.
In this, you also have constipation like epidemic,
so let's start the video
First of all we will login to the iMobile application
If you have
not downloaded and activated this application yet, then
we have given the link in the description from
there, from there you can activate it
and see, on the home page as soon as we log in,
we will be shown the option of Investment and Share,
we will click on this option
and on clicking we will see that here below
we are shown an option of
Health and Travel Cover, so we will
click on this Health Cover option
and on clicking we will see the next page will open,
here you will get the option of buying a health insurance
policy, then you
will see here you will click on the Buy 9 Owner button,
as soon as you click on Bhai Na Ho here,
your next page will open here
So look, we click on Buy 9 here
and click on
Next, our page has opened. Here at the
top
it is asking for your name, so
you will enter your name here. After that, you will
see on the second line here that it is asking for your date of birth, so
you will enter your date of birth.
After that, if someone asks you if there is an
existing thing, then you can say yes or no to it
and after that you will click on the profit button.
Like, when you click on profit here,
your page will open on Next.
Here it will ask you about the time limit,
how much time limit you
want to take, so you will get cover up to a minimum of 5 lakhs and a maximum of
25 lakhs.
After that, the
bank provides all the facilities here that you
can also take OPD cover here, so
you can add it by clicking on OPD here. So, see,
we have added OPD here
and after that, see here the total
amount that we are paying is ₹7500 ₹5 and this is a
direct tweet from our account.  If it goes,
we click on the Profit button
and select our account here.
Now, when it opens, click on Next.
Look, it is asking for your Nomica information.
First, name, then relationship, and
then date of birth. We will fill in all the details here.
After that, we will see below
that it is asking for employee records. So,
friends, if any of your employees is
helping you
in purchasing this policy, then you
can paste their employee ID here. Otherwise, you
can click on the Profit button. As soon as
you click on the Submit button, your page will
open where you can enter all the details here.
Confirmation will be given.
Check all these details once. The
premium of your group health insurance policy is linked
and after that, click on this account number button here.
You will submit it. As soon as you
submit, you will see that you will
receive a message that your policy has been successfully purchased. After that, you will get the
application number here. So,
friends, in this way, you can take an online health insurance policy sitting at home.
Friends, if you liked the video then
like this video and subscribe to this channel
because on this channel
we keep bringing new information related to your health,
so subscribe to this channel
and see you in the next video, till then
thank you.